blabbermouth.net 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Blabbermouth.net

BLABBERMOUTH.NET PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: August 14, 2013

The owner of BLABBERMOUTH.NET understands your interest in your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how it applies to the collection and use of information gathered when you visit the Blabbermouth.net website (“Site”). Except as specifically stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies to our Site and is not applicable to other web sites or to the practices of other third party services that you may access from or through our Site. More generally, this policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control. 

Your use of this Site represents your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you don't agree with any of these terms, please stop using the Site. From time to time, our Privacy Policy may be updated and, when it is, we will change the "Last Updated" date above and post the changes to this page. Each visit to the Site by you shall signify your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy that is in existence at the time of your visit. By visiting and using the Site after an update, you signify your agreement to be bound by the updated terms, so please check this page from time to time. 

Not Targeting Children

This Site is not intended for children and we currently do not knowingly collect or aggregate personally identifiable information regarding children younger than 13 years old. If you are under 13 years old, please note that you should not provide any personally identifiable information and should discontinue any use of this Site.

Cookies and Information Collected from You

Blabbermouth and/or its website hosting service provider(s) (hereinafter, "we" or "us") uses cookies to receive and/or record certain non-personally identifiable information about you as you visit and navigate the Site. Non-personally identifiable information, by itself, does not reveal your identity but refers, instead, to anonymous information and can include things like your IP address and information about how you navigate through the Site. 

Cookies are tiny text files that may be saved on your computer that we can read when you visit our Site. We use session cookies to facilitate Site navigation and for other administrative and internal purposes. Session cookies and the information in them are deleted when you close out of your browser software session. It is not our policy to retain such information after your browser session is completed. Most or all Internet browsers provide a procedure for you to prevent or block the use of cookies. If you wish to generally block cookies, please consult the documentation for your browser although doing so may impact your use of the Site.

Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons and Information Used for Advertising

Pages viewed on this Site may contain embedded links to files hosted and/or served by third parties such as YouTube® or links to third party web pages and/or web sites ( collectively [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)). They may also display third party advertising (AThird Party [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)) served by third party Ad Server companies (“Ad Servers”) that We allow to serve ads (AThird Party [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)). These Ad Servers may use cookies or web beacons ( clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies) or similar technologies to collect and/or store certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Site, as well as during your visits to third party Web sites you may click through to from our Site, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you.

When you click on any Links or Third Party Ads displayed on this Site that take you away from the Site, you will view any resulting content on a web page not controlled, maintained or operated by us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided by You or collected at third parties’ web pages. We recommend You contact the owners of such third party web pages or Third Party Ads providers for further information on their privacy practices.

Google Analytics. We may use Google Analytics, an online analytics tool provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), that uses cookies to assist web site operators in analyzing usage of their web sites for marketing, usablility and similar purposes by compiling and making reports available concerning how visitors interact with a website. These cookies, placed by Google, collect and store non-personally identifiable information to measure and evaluate Your use the Web site. For further information on Google Analytics and how it functions, please visit: https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html . 

We also license certain of our trademarks to a branded Blabbermouth.net store. This store features merchandise that we think will be of interest to our visitors. The store, however, is operated, owned and maintained by third parties with their own privacy and cookie policies that we do not control. 

The only personally identifiable information about you directly received by us is personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us. Generally, personally identifiable information is used for the purposes for which you have provided it (for example, to provide you credit for a news item which you submitted). 

For example, if you choose to submit potential news stories to us by sending us an email, we will have your email address and any other personal information you choose to provide, such as your name or nickname, if you want to request credit for the submission. These emails are sent to us at a Gmail® account used by us for such purposes and that are owned and maintained by Google. Through the Gmail® service, we may retain such email correspondence and the information contained in it. Should you disclose your name/nickname and/or website by voluntarily providing it for credit, then, to the extent we include such information as the source of the story on the Site, it will be public and available for Site visitors to see.

Separately, you can submit comments on news stories or CD and DVD reviews by means of the Facebook® social plugin used by the Site. Once you are logged into an active Facebook® account, You can submit a comment on CD and DVD reviews posted on the Site. Once You do, certain personally identifiable information about you, such as your Facebook® screen name and/or profile picture will be visible to other Site visitors as well as to us. You may delete a comment from your Facebook® account. Once you do, your Facebook® screen name and/or associated Facebook® profile photo will be visible on the Site and any information you provide may be visible and/or accessible to other Facebook® users in accordance with Facebook policies. For further information on privacy issues concerning the Facebook social plug in, please visit https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other#socialplugin . 

We reserve the right to ban users from the Site and/or to hide or block User comments to CD/DVD reviews under appropriate circumstances, as set forth in our Terms of Service Agreement.

Should you choose to follow our Twitter page, We can see You as a follower of Blabbermouth. By signing up to use the Twitter service, you are agreeing to be bound by Twitter’s terms of service and Twitter’s privacy policies, which are separate from those of our Site.

By subscribing to our RSS Feed, we will have access to certain non-personally identifiable information, such as your computer’s IP address, which is used to identify your computer as the computer requesting the updated RSS Feed. We use this information to deliver the updated content to your RSS reader software agent.

Sharing of Information Collected

Generally, we do not retain non-personally identifiable information recorded by us when you use the Site beyond the close of your browser session. Nevertheless, because non-personally identifiable information collected at the Site does not personally identify you, we reserve the right to share non-personally identifiable information that we may receive with any affiliates and/or other third parties, for any purpose. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy we do not rent, sell, or share personally identifiable information about you with others. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to disclose any information which we may obtain, and otherwise cooperate with, any orders or process of legal authorities and/or Courts and/or subpoenas by law enforcement or similar agencies and/or lawfully issued in the context of criminal or civil litigation or other judicial, quasi judicial or other dispute resolution proceeding. We also reserve the right to disclose any information which we may obtain when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding: illegal activities; in connection with suspected fraud, intellectual property infringement; situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person; violations of Blabbermouth's Terms of Use Agreement; or as otherwise required or permitted by law. Additionally, we may share any information we have with any successors, joint venture partners or similar entities in the course of business. 

If we have personally identifiable information of yours, such as your email address, we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Blabbermouth service, such as service announcements, administrative messages, newsletters, or notifications of Site updates.

Privacy Protection Measures and Opt Out Choices: 

In many cases, browser settings and third party software may be used by you to limit or eliminate cookies stored on your computer. We do not implement any special safeguards for such purposes nor provide any method for You to opt out or modify any such information, other than the right to delete comments you post to the Site through use of the Facebook® social plugin, as explained above. 

You may consult the privacy practices of your Internet access provider with respect to any options you have concerning information collected or stored by them. You may also be able to opt out of certain third party tracking technologies used by Ad Servers by following opt out procedures offered at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ and http://www.adtech.com/en/service/cookies.html. Please note that these web pages are offered by third parties and may be moved, changed, modified or discontinued by them, at their sole discretion. We have no responsibility for the continued availability of such web pages or opt-out services offered there. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Personally Identifiable Information

Due to the limited nature of personally identifiable information about you that we receive, there are currently no preferences for you to select to delete personally identifiable information voluntarily provided at the Site except for the ability of users who post comments through Facebook® to delete same from public view on the Site. We also do not provide for opt outs of any personally identifiable information You voluntarily provide to us by email. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to determine whether to keep emails and/or how to keep them and/or for how long to keep them.

If You are still concerned about any other information that may be collected by Your use of the Site, You should refrain from continuing to visit the Site. 

Relationship of this Policy to our Terms of Use Agreement

Use of our Site is also subject to our Terms of Use Agreement ("TOS") which is [available here](http://blabbermouth.net/terms-of-service). The terms of this privacy policy are incorporated into the TOS.

Our TOS provides for us to obtain certain rights in the information and materials that you may provide to the Site. In addition, our TOS contains certain liability and warranty limitations and/or disclaimers which apply to any non-compliance by us with this Privacy Policy.

How to Contact BLABBERMOUTH.NET 

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) You may also contact us by writing to:

BLABBERMOUTH.NET   
P.O. Box 8200   
White Plains, NY 10602   
USA
